Sculpture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- France (Box 4)
  - 20th Century [Slide box 21] (Box 4)
    - Duchamp-Villon, Raymond, 1876-1918 (Box 5)
      - New York (Box 5)
        - Various Titles (Box 5)
      - Paris (Box 5)
        - Various Titles (Box 5)
    - Dupre, Guillaume, 1576-1643 (Box 5)
    - Etienne-Martin, 1913- (Box 5)
    - Falconet, Etienne Maurice, 1716-1791 (Box 5)
    - Fautrier, Jean, 1898-1964 (Box 5)
    - Fauveau, Felice de, 1802-1886 (Box 5)
    - Filliou, Robert, 1926-1987 (Box 5)
    - Fremiet, Emmanuel, 1824-1911 (Box 5)
    - Fremin, Rene, 1672-1744 (Box 5)
    - Fresnaya, Roger de la, 1885-1925 (Box 5)
    - Garnier-Brzeska, Henri, 1891-1915 (Box 5)
    - Gauguin, Paul, 1848-1903 [Slide boxes 26-27] (Box 5)
    - Gericault, Theodore, 1791-1824 [Slide box 27] (Box 5)
    - Girardon, Francois, 1628-1715 (Box 5)
    - Giraud, P.F.G., 1783-1836 (Box 5)
    - Gois, Etienne P.A., 1731-1823 (Box 5)
    - Goujon, Jean, 1510-1568 (Box 5)
    - Guimard, Hector, 1867-1942 (Box 5)
    - Herold, Jacques, 1910- (Box 5)
    - Houdon, Jean Antoine, 1741-1828 (Box 5)
      - New York (Box 5)
        - Various Titles (Box 5)
      - Paris (Box 5)
        - Various Titles (Box 5)
      - Washington (Box 5)
        - Various Titles (Box 5)
    - Hugnet, Georges, 1906-1974 (Box 5)
    - Hugo, Valentine (Box 5)
    - Huyghe, Pierre, 1962- (Box 5)
    - Ipousteguy, Jean, 1920- (Box 5)
    - Jacquet, Mathieu, b. 1550 [Slide box 28] (Box 5)
    - Jean De Cambrai, d. 1438 (Box 5)
    - Jean de Liege, d. 1382 (Box 5)
    - Jean, Marcel (Box 5)
    - Julien, Pierre, 1731-1804 (Box 5)
    - Klein, Yves, 1928-1962 (Box 5)
    - Koman, Ilhan (Box 5)
    - Lacombe, Georges, 1868-1916 (Box 5)
    - Larche, Raoul, 1860-1912 (Box 5)
    - Laurens, Henri, 1885-1954 (Box 5)
    - Lavier, Bertrand, 1949- (Box 5)
    - Le Clerc & S. Priest, J. (Box 5)
    - Leccia, Ange, 1952- (Box 5)
    - Lecomte, Felix, 1737-1817 (Box 5)
    - Le Corbusier (Box 5)
    - Le Faguays, Pierre, 1892- (Box 5)
    - Leger, Fernand, 1881-1955 (Box 5)
      Xx Sculpture France
    - Legros, Pierre, 1629-1714 (Box 5)
    - Legros, Pierre Younger, 1666-1719 (Box 5)
      Xx for Altar of S. Luigi Gonzaga – Architecture Renaissance Italy Rome Churches S. Ignazio
    - Le Lorrain, Robert, 1666-1743 (Box 5)
    - Lemot, Frederic, 1773-1827 (Box 5)
    - Lemoyne, Jean-Baptiste, 1704-1778 (Box 5)
    - Leymone, Jean-Louis, 1665-1755 (Box 5)
    - Le Sueur, Hubert, 1580-1670 (Box 5)
    - Lipchitz, Jacques, 1891-1973 [Slide box 29] (Box 5)
      - Merion, PA (Box 5)
        - Bather III (Box 5)
      - New Haven (Box 5)
        - Various Titles (Box 5)
      - New York (Box 5)
        - Various Titles (Box 5)
    - Maillol, Aristide, 1861-1944 (Box 5)
    - Marey, E.J., 1830-1904 (Box 5)
    - Marende, Jean, c. 1502 (Box 5)
    - Marlet, J.H. (Box 5)
    - Marque, Albert, 1872-? (Box 5)
    - Marsy, B. & G. [Slide box 30] (Box 5)
    - Masson, Andre, 1896- (Box 5)
    - Matisse, Henri, 1869-1954 (Box 5)
    - Mellot, Guiraud (School of) (Box 5)
    - Mene, Pierre Jules, 1810-1879 (Box 5)
    - Moitte, Jean-Guillaume, 1746-1810 (Box 5)
    - Monnot, Pierre E., 1657-1733 (Box 5)
    - Morellet, Francois, 1926- (Box 5)
    - L'Orme, Philibert & P. Bontemps (Box 5)
    - Orlan, 1947- (Box 5)
    - Pajou, Augustin, 1730-1809 (Box 5)
    - Picabia, Francis, 1879-1953 (Box 5)
    - Pelle, Honore (Box 5)
    - Picault, Emile-Louis, ca. 1900- (Box 5)
    - Pigalle, Jean-Baptiste, 1714-1785 (Box 5)
    - Pilon, Germain, 1535-1590 [Slide boxes 30-31] (Box 5–6)
    - Poirier, Anne & Patrick [Slide box 31] (Box 6)
    - Preault, Auguste, 1809-1879 (Box 6)
    - Prieur, Barthelemy, ca.1611- (Box 6)
    - Prou, Jacques, 1655-1706 (Box 6)
    - Puget, Pierre, 1620-1694 (Box 6)
    - Ramey, Claude, 1754-1838 (Box 6)
    - Raysse, Martial, 1936- (Box 6)
    - Regnault, Guillaume, 1450-1531 (Box 6)
    - Renoir, Pierre-Auguste, 1841-1919 (Box 6)
    - Richier, Germaine, 1904-1959 (Box 6)
    - Richier, Ligier, ca.1500-1567 (Box 6)
    - Roche, Pierre, 1855-1922 (Box 6)
    - Rodin, Auguste, 1840-1917 (Box 6)
      - Figures (Box 6)
        - Age of Bronze (Box 6)
        - Balzac (Box 6)
        - The Thinker [Slide box 32] (Box 6)
      - Gates of Hell (Box 6)
      - Groups (Box 6)
        - Burghers of Calais (Box 6)
      - Heads (Box 6)
    - Rognier, Henri-Victor, 1758-? (Box 6)
    - Roland, Philippe-L., 1746-1816 (Box 6)
    - Roubiliac, Louis Francois, 1695-1762 (Box 6)
    - Roux-Colas, Anne-Marie, 1898- (Box 6)
    - Rude, Francois, 1784-1855 (Box 6)
    - Saly, Jacques, 1717-1776 (Box 6)
    - Saupique, Georges, 1889-1961 (Box 6)
    - Schoffer, Nicolas, 1912- (Box 6)
    - Sluter, Claus, ca.1375-1405 (Box 6)
      - Portal Group (Box 6)
      - Tomb of Jean Sans Peur [Slide boxes 32-33] (Box 6)
      - Tomb of Philippe le Hard [Slide box 33] (Box 6)
      - Well of Moses (Box 6)
    - Spoerri, Daniel, 1930- (Box 6)
    - Stouf, Jean B., 1742-1826 (Box 6)
    - Takis, 1925- (Box 6)
    - Tangui, Yves, 1900-1955 (Box 6)
    - Theodon, Jean-Baptiste, 1646-1713 (Box 6)
    - Tubi, Jean-B., 1630/36-1700 (Box 6)
    - Vasarely, Victor (Box 6)
- Germany (Box 6)
  [Slide box 34]
  - 10th Century (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - 11th Century (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
    - Hildesheim (Box 6)
    - Werden (Box 6)
  - 12th Century (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - 13th Century (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - 14th Century (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - 15th Century (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - 16th Century [Slide box 35] (Box 6)
    - Various Titles (Box 6)
  - 17th – 20th Centuries (Box 6)
    - Various Art (Box 6)
    - Althoff, Kai, 1966- (Box 6)
    - Alvermann, Hans Peter, act. c. 1965 (Box 6)
    - Ardt, Olaf, 1961- (Box 6)
    - Arp, Hans, 1887-1966 (Box 6)
    - Asam, Egid Quirin, 1692-1750 (Box 6)
    - Balkenhol, Stephen, 1957- (Box 6)
    - Ball, Hugo, 1886-1927 (Box 6)
    - Barlach, Ernst, 1870-1938 (Box 6)
    - Baselitz, Georg, 1938- (Box 6)
    - Bauermeister, Mary H.R, 1934- (Box 6)
    - Baugarten, Lothar, 1949- (Box 6)
    - Bayer, Herbert, 1900-1986 (Box 6)
    - Belling, Rudolf, 1886- (Box 6)
    - Bellmer, Hans, 1902-1975 (Box 6)
    - Beuys, Joseph, 1921-1986 (Box 6)
      - Various (Box 6)
      - 1950-1959 [Slide box 36] (Box 6)
        - Various Titles (Box 6)
      - 1960-1965 (Box 6)
        - Various Titles (Box 6)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 6)
        - Various Titles (Box 6)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 6)
        - Various Titles (Box 6)
      - 1970-1973 [Slide box 37] (Box 7)
        - Various Titles (Box 7)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 7)
        - Various Titles (Box 7)
      - 1976- (Box 7)
        - Various Titles (Box 7)
    - Braun, Anton (Box 7)
    - Braun, Matti, 1968- (Box 7)
    - Brehmer, K.P., 1938- (Box 7)
    - Breker, Arno, 1900- (Box 7)
    - Bruggemann, Hans (Box 7)
    - Brunning, Peter, 1929- (Box 7)
    - Brus, Gunter, 1938- (Box 7)
    - Buthe, Michael, 1944- (Box 7)
    - Buttner, Werner, 1954- (Box 7)
    - Christian, Johann J., 1706-1777 (Box 7)
    - Christiansen, Henning, 1932- (Box 7)
    - Dancher, Hans (Box 7)
    - Dannecker, Johann, 1758-1841 (Box 7)
    - Darboven, Hanne, 1941- (Box 7)
    - Davmiller, A. [Slide box 38] (Box 7)
    - Dell, Peter (the elder), b.1501 (Box 7)
    - Durer, Albrecht, 1471-1528 (Box 7)
    - Egell, Paul, 1691-1752 (Box 7)
    - Erhart, Gregor, 1460-1540 (Box 7)
    - Eehart, Michael, 1469-1552 (Box 7)
    - Ernst, Max, 1891-1976 (Box 7)
    - Feldmann, Hans Peter, 1941- (Box 7)
    - Feuchtmeyer, Joseph A., 1696-1770 (Box 7)
    - Fisher, Lother, 1923- (Box 7)
    - Freytag-Loringhoeven, Elsa von, 1874-1927 (Box 7)
    - Fritsch, Katharina, 1956- (Box 7)
    - Gaudnek, Walter (Box 7)
    - Gelmacher, Klaus, 1940- (Box 7)
    - Gerhaert, Nicholas, 1462-1473 (Box 7)
    - Giese, Imi, 1942-1974 [Slide box 39] (Box 7)
    - Gotz, Joseph Matthias, 1696-1760 (Box 7)
    - Grasser, Erasmus, 1450-1526 (Box 7)
    - Graevenitz, Gerhard von, 1934- (Box 7)
    - Gunther, Franz Ignaz, 1725-1775 (Box 7)
    - Haacke, Hans, 1936- [Slide boxes 39-40] (Box 7)
    - Haese, Gunter, 1924- [Slide box 40] (Box 7)
    - Hagenauer, Friedrich (Box 7)
    - Hartung, Hans, 1904- (Box 7)
    - Hartung, Karl, 1908- (Box 7)
    - Hauser, Erich, 1930- (Box 7)
    - Heckel, Erich, 1883-1970 (Box 7)
    - Heerich, Erwin, 1922- (Box 7)
    - Heiliger, Bernhard, 1915- (Box 7)
    - Hering, Loy, ca.1484/5-1554 (Box 7)
    - Herold, Gerog, 1947- (Box 7)
    - Hesse, Eva, 1936-1970 (Box 7)
      - -1965 (Box 7)
      - 1966-1968 (Box 7)
      - 1969-1970 [Slide boxes 40-41] (Box 7)
    - Heyde, Henning von den, 1487-1520 [Slide box 41] (Box 7)
    - Hirschhorn, Thomas, 1957- (Box 7)
    - Hodicke, K.H. (Box 7)
    - Hofer, Candida, 1944- (Box 7)
    - Hoke, Bernhard, act. c. 1690- (Box 7)
    - Holderman, Georg, 1610-1629 (Box 7)
    - Honert, Martin, 1953 (Box 7)
    - Immendorff, Jorg, 1945- (Box 7)
    - Itten, Johannes, 1888- [Slide box 42] (Box 7)
      X Itten, Johannes (workshop)
    - Jorhan, Christian, elder, 1727-1804 (Box 7)
    - Juchtzer, Christian, 1752-1812 (Box 7)
    - Kaschauer, Jakob (Box 7)
    - Kels, Hans, the elder, 1480/85-1559 (Box 7)
    - Kiefer, Anselm, 1945- (Box 7)
    - Kipperberger, Martin, 1953- (Box 7)
    - Kirchner, Ernst, 1880-1938 (Box 7)
    - Klinger, Max, 1857-1920 (Box 7)
    - Knoebel, Imi, 1943- (Box 7)
    - Kolbe, Georg, 1877-1974 (Box 7)
    - Kollwitz, Kathe, 1867-1945 (Box 7)
    - Kraft, Adam, 1450-1509 (Box 7)
    - Kricke, Norbert, 1922- (Box 7)
    - Lehmbruck, Wilhelm, 1881-1919 (Box 7)
      - Various Titles (Box 7)
      - The Bather (Box 7)
      - Contemplative Woman (Box 7)
      - Fallen Warrior (Box 7)
      - Female Torsos (Box 7)
      - Kneeling Woman (Box 7)
      - Rising Youth (Box 7)
      - Seated Youth (Box 7)
      - Standing Woman [Slide box 43] (Box 8)
    - Leinsberger, Hans, ac.1513-1530 (Box 8)
    - Lenk, Kaspar Thomas, 1933- (Box 8)
    - Lueg, Konrad, 1939-1996 (Box 8)
    - Lupertz, Markus, 1941- (Box 8)
    - Luther, Adolf (Box 8)
    - Mack, Otto-Heinz, 1931- (Box 8)
      Xx for comparison between Mack's Sahara Relief & Pyramid of Cheops see Arch. Egypt Gizeh Pyramid of Cheops (3x4)
    - Marcks, Gerhard, 1889- (Box 8)
    - Mattner, Jakob (Box 8)
    - Meit, Conrad, ac.1500-1544 (Box 8)
    - Merz, Gerhard, 1947- (Box 8)
    - Metzel, Olaf, 1952- (Box 8)
    - Mucha, Reinhard (Box 8)
    - Multscher, Hans, 1400-1467 (Box 8)
    - Munstermann, Ludwig, 1575-1637 (Box 8)
    - Notke, Bernt, 1440-1509 (Box 8)
    - Obrist, Hermann, 1863-1927 (Box 8)
    - Odenbach, Marcel, 1953- (Box 8)
    - Oehlen, Albert, 1954- (Box 8)
    - Pacher, Michael, 1435-1498 (Box 8)
    - Paeffgen, C.O., 1933- (Box 8)
    - Palermo, Blinky (Peter), 1943-1977 (Box 8)
    - Penck, A.R., 1939- [Slide boxes 43-44] (Box 8)
    - Permoser, Balthasar, 1651-1732 [Slide box 44] (Box 8)
    - Petel, Georg, 1590-1634 (Box 8)
    - Piene, Otto, 1928- (Box 8)
    - Pilgram, Franz A., 1460-1515 (Box 8)
    - Polzig, Hans & Marlene Moeschke (Box 8)
    - Rauch, C.D., 1777-1857 (Box 8)
    - Reinecke, Chris, act. c.1965 (Box 8)
    - Rheinsberg, Raffael, 1943- (Box 8)
    - Riemenschneider, Tilman, 1460-1531 (Box 8)
      - Various Titles (Box 8)
      - Bamberg (Box 8)
        - Tomb of Kaiser Heinrich II (Box 8)
      - Berlin (Box 8)
      - Greglingen (Box 8)
      - Detwang (Box 8)
      - Munich (Box 8)
      - Nurmberg (Box 8)
      - Rothenburg [Slide boxes 44-45] (Box 8)
      - Wuzburg [Slide box 45] (Box 8)
        - Various Titles (Box 8)
        - Adam & Eve Figures (Box 8)
        - S. Burchard of Wurzburg (Box 8)
    - Rietschel, Ernst, 1840-1861 (Box 8)
    - Roth, Dieter, 1930-1998 (Box 8)
    - Rumbach, Johan F. (Box 8)
    - Ruthenbeck, Reiner, 1937- (Box 8)
    - Schadow, J.G., 1764-1850 (Box 8)
    - Schlemmer, Oskar, 1988-1943 (Box 8)
    - Schmidt-Rottluff, K., 1884-1976 (Box 8)
    - Schongauer, Martin, 15th Century (Box 8)
    - Schwitters, Kurt, 1887-1948 (Box 8)
    - Slominski, Andreas, 1959- (Box 8)
    - Stoss, Veit, 1447-1542 (Box 8)
    - Stumpf, Manfred [Slide box 46] (Box 8)
    - Syrlin, Jorg, ? -1491 (Box 8)
    - Teusch, Dieter (Box 8)
    - Thorak, Josef, 1889-1952 (Box 8)
    - Trockel, Rosemarie, 1952- (Box 8)
    - Uecker, Gunther, 1930- (Box 8)
    - Uhlmann, Hans, 1900- (Box 8)
    - Ulay and Marina (Box 8)
    - Vischer, Peter, the Elder, 1460-1529 (Box 8)
      Xx Vischer, Peter & family for Tomb of Maximilian figures see sculpture Germany 16th century.
    - Vischer, Peter the Younger, 1487-1528 (Box 8)
    - Vostell, Wolf, 1932- (Box 8)
    - Voth, Hannsjorg, 1940- (Box 8)
    - Waldschmidt, Arnold, 1873-1958 (Box 8)
    - Walther, Franz Erhard, 1939- (Box 8)
    - Werwerka, Stephen, act. c.1960 [Slide box 47] (Box 8)
    - Wilding, Ludwig, 1927- (Box 8)
    - Zero group, ac.1958-1966 (Box 8)
      X Mack, Piene and Uecker
      Xx Miscellaneous Movements- Zero
    - Zurn, Martin, 1590-1665 (Box 8)
- Greece (Box 8)
  - Various Artists (Box 8)
- Holland (Box 8)
  - Various Artists (Box 8)
  - Andersen, Gunnar Aagaard, 1919-1982 (Box 8)
  - Appel, Karel, 1921- (Box 8)
  - Arnt van Tricht, ca. 1540-1553 (Box 8)
  - Berns, Ben, 1936- (Box 8)
  - Cure, Cornelius & William II (Box 8)
  - Dibbets, Jan, 1941- (Box 8)
  - Keyser, Hendrick de, 1565-1631 (Box 8)
  - Vantongerloo, Georges, 1886- (Box 8)
  - Vries, Adriaen de, 1560-1626 (Box 8)
    - Various Titles (Box 8)
    - Detroit (Box 8)
    - Drottningholm (Box 8)
    - Vienna (Box 8)
    - Washington (Box 8)
- Hungary (Box 8)
  - Various Artists (Box 8)
  - Moholy-Nagy, Laszlo, 1895-1946 (Box 8)
- Iraq (Box 8)
  [Slide box 48]
  - Rahal, Khalid Al-, 1926-1987 (Box 8)
- Israel (Box 8)
  - Agam, Yaacov, 1928- (Box 8)
- Italy (Box 8)
  - Various Titles (Box 8)
- Romanesque (Box 8)
  - 11th century (Box 8)
    - Various titles (Box 8)
    - Rome, S. Paolo: Bronze Doors (Box 8)
    - Verona: Bronze Doors (Box 8)
  - 12th century (Box 8)
    - Various artists (Box 8)
    - Canosa: Bronze Doors (Box 8)
    - Milan, Porta Romana: Reliefs (Box 8)
    - Pisa: Bronze Doors (Box 8)
      Xx Bonannus of Pisa
  - 13th century (Box 8)
    - Various titles (Box 8)
    - S. Peter, bronze in S. Peter's (Box 8)
- Renaissance (Box 9)
  [Slide box 49]
  - Various titles (Box 9)
  - 14th century (Box 9)
    Xx Other Scaligeri Tomb, see Bonino da Campione Tomb of Can Signorio Verna, S. Maria Antica
    - Various titles (Box 9)
    - Porto Della Mandorla (Box 9)
  - 15th century (Box 9)
    - Various Titles (Box 9)
    - Arco D'Alfonso D'Aragona (Box 9)
    - Tomb of King Ladislaus (Box 9)
    - Tomb of Maria Piccolomini (Box 9)
  - 16th century (Box 9)
    - Various Titles [Slide boxes 49-50] (Box 9)
  - 17th century [Slide box 50] (Box 9)
    - Various titles (Box 9)
    - Varallo Sacro Monte (Box 9)
      Xx for exteriors of chapels Arch. Renn. Italy Varallo
  - 18th –19th centuries (Box 9)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 9)
  - 20th century (Box 9)
    - Various Artists (Box 9)
    - Adriano Fiorentino, ca. 15th century (Box 9)
    - Agostino di Duccio, 1418-1498 (Box 9)
    - Agostino di Giovanni, 1269-1348 (Box 9)
    - Alberti, Leon B., 1404-1472 (Box 9)
    - Algardi, Alessandro, 1598-1654 (Box 9)
    - Amadeo, Giovanni A., 1477-1522 [Slide boxes 50-51] (Box 9)
    - Ammanati, Bartolomeo, 1511-1592 [Slide box 51] (Box 9)
    - Angeli, Franco, 1935-1988 (Box 9)
    - Anselmo, Giovanni, 1934- (Box 9)
    - Antelami, Benedetto, ca.1150-1230 (Box 9)
    - L'Antico (P.J.A. Bonacolsi), 1460-1528 (Box 9)
    - Antonio Federighi, 1420-1490 (Box 9)
    - Arnoldi, Alberto, ca.1351-1364 (Box 9)
    - Arnolfo di Cambio, 1260-1302 (Box 9)
    - Aspetti, Tiziano, 1565-1607 (Box 9)
    - Aurai, G. Domenico d' (Box 9)
    - Balla, Giacomo, 1871-1958 (Box 9)
    - Banco, Nanni di, ca. 1383-1471 (Box 9)
      Xx for Porta della Mandorla, Florence Duomo, also Arch. Gothic Italy Florence Cathedral and Sculpture 14th century Porta della Mandorla
    - Bandinelli, Baccio, 1488-1560 [Slide box 52] (Box 9)
    - Bandini, Giovanni, 1540-1599 (Box 9)
    - Baratta, Francesco, d.1666 (Box 9)
    - Baroncelli, Nicolo di Giovanni, ca.1434-1453 (Box 9)
    - Bartoldo di Giovanni, 1420-1491 (Box 9)
    - Bartolini, Lorenzo, 1777-1850 (Box 9)
    - Bellano, Bartolomeo, 1434-1497 (Box 9)
    - Belliazzi, Raffaele, 1835-ca.1905 (Box 9)
    - Benedetto da Maiano, 1442-1497 (Box 9)
    - Bernini, Giovanni Lorenzo, 1598-1680 (Box 9)
      - Berlin (Box 9)
      - Cambridge (Box 9)
      - Detroit (Box 9)
      - Florence (Box 9)
      - London (Box 9)
      - Rome [Slide box 53] (Box 9)
        - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - Elephant and Obelisk (Box 9)
        - Triton Fountain (Box 9)
        - Borghese Gallery (Box 9)
          - Aeneas, Anchises & Ascanius (Box 9)
          - Apollo & Daphne (Box 9)
          - Cardinal Scipione Borghese (Box 9)
          - David (Box 9)
          - Louis XIV (Box 9)
          - Rape of Proserpine [Slide box 54] (Box 9)
          - Truth Unveiled (Box 9)
        - Palace Barberine (Box 9)
          - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - Piazza Navona (Box 9)
          - Fountain of 4 Rivers (Box 9)
          - Fontana Del Moro (Box 9)
        - Ponte S. Angelo (Box 9)
          - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - S. Andrea Delle Fratte (Box 9)
          - Various Titles (Box 9)
        - S. Francisco a Ripa (Box 9)
          - Blessed Ludovica (Box 9)
        - S. Lorenzo in Lucina (Box 9)
          - Gabriele Fonseca (Box 9)
        - S. Maria di Moserrato (Box 9)
          - Busto of Monsignor Pedro de Foix Montoya (Box 9)
        - S. Maria Del Popole [Slide box 55] (Box 10)
          - Various Titles (Box 10)
        - S. Maria della Vittoria (Box 10)
          - Cornaro Chapel (Box 10)
            - S. Teresa Altar (Box 10)
        - S. Maria Sopra Minerva (Box 10)
          - Various Titles (Box 10)
        - S. Peter's (Box 10)
          - Various Titles (Box 10)
          - Altar/Chapel of Blessed Sacrament (Box 10)
          - Altar & Chair of S. Peter (Box 10)
          - S. Longinus (Box 10)
          - Tomb of Alexander VII (Box 10)
          - Tomb of Urban VIII [Slide box 56] (Box 10)
        - Vatican (Box 10)
          - Various Titles (Box 10)
      - Siena (Box 10)
        - Various Titles (Box 10)
      - Stockholm (Box 10)
        - Various Titles (Box 10)
      - Versailles (Box 10)
        - Louis XIV (Box 10)
      - Washington (Box 10)
        - Various Titles (Box 10)
    - Bernini, Pietro, 1562-1622 (Box 10)
    - Bertoldo Di Giovanni, 1410-1491 (Box 10)
    - Biasi, Alberto, 1937- (Box 10)
    - Boccioni, Umberto, 1882-1916 (Box 10)
    - Boetti, Alighiero, 1940- (Box 10)
    - Bolgi, Andrea, 1605-1656 (Box 10)
    - Bonannus of Pisa, ca.1174-1196 (Box 10)
    - Bonino da Campione, ca.1349-1397 (Box 10)
    - Boscoli, Tommaso di Pietro, 1503-1574 (Box 10)
    - Bregno, Antonio (attributed) (Box 10)
    - Bregno, Andrea, 1418-1508 (Box 10)
    - Briosco, Andrea, 1470-1532 [Slide box 57] (Box 10)
      - Various titles (Box 10)
      - Washington (Box 10)
        - Various titles (Box 10)
    - Brunelleschi, Filippo, 1377-1446 (Box 10)
    - Buggiano (Andrea di Lazzaro Cavalcanti) (Box 10)
      X Buggiano (Andrea Cavalcanti)
    - Buon, Bartolommeo (Box 10)
      Xx for overall view and Diagram of the Porta della Carta see Arch. Gothic Italy Venice Doge's Palace
    - Bussotti, Sylvno, 1931- (Box 10)
    - Busti, Agostino, 1483-1548 (Box 10)
    - Buzio, Ippolito (Box 10)
    - Caccini, Giovanni, 1562-1612 (Box 10)
    - Caffa, Melchiorre, 1635-1667 (Box 10)
    - Calzolari, Pier Paolo, 1943- (Box 10)
    - Cambellotti, Duilio, 1876-1960 (Box 10)
    - Cametti, Bernardino, 1669-1736 (Box 10)
    - Campagna, Giorolamo, 1552-ca.1623 (Box 10)
    - Canova, Antonio, 1757-1822 [Slide box 58] (Box 10)
      - Various titles (Box 10)
      - Florence (Box 10)
        - Venus (Box 10)
      - Rome (Box 10)
        - Borghese Gallery (Box 10)
          - Pauline Bonaparte Borghese (Box 10)
        - S. Peter's (Box 10)
          - Various titles (Box 10)
      - Vienna (Box 10)
        - Tomb of Maria Christina (Box 10)
    - Carlini, Agostino, ca.1760-1790 (Box 10)
    - Cattaneo, Danese, 1508-1573 (Box 10)
    - Cattelan, Maurizio, 1960- (Box 10)
    - Celebrano, Francesco, 1729-1814 (Box 10)
    - Cellini, Benvenuto, 1500-1571 (Box 10)
      - Florence (Box 10)
        - Various Titles (Box 10)
        - Perseus (Box 10)
        - Cosimo I de'Medici [Slide box 59] (Box 10)
      - Vienna (Box 10)
        - Salt Cellar of Francis I (Box 10)
      - Washington (Box 10)
        - Virtue Overcomes Vice (Box 10)
    - Cerachi, Giusepe, 1751-1801 (Box 10)
    - Ciuffagni, Bernardo (attributed) (Box 10)
    - Civitale, Matteo, 1436-1501 (Box 10)
    - Clemente, Francesco, 1952- (Box 10)
    - Colla, Etore, 1899- (Box 10)
    - Consagra, Pietro, 1920- (Box 10)
    - Cornacchini, Agostino, 1685- after 1754 (Box 10)
    - Corradini, Antonio, ca.1695-1752 (Box 10)
    - Cucchi, Enzo, 1951- (Box 10)
    - Dalmata, Giovanni, 1440-1576 (Box 10)
    - Danti, Vincenzo, 1530-1576 (Box 10)
    - Depero, Fortunato, 1892-1960 (Box 10)
    - De Santis, A. (Box 10)
    - Desiderio da Settignano, 1428-1464 (Box 10)
      - Various Titles (Box 10)
      - Florence (Box 10)
        - Various Titles (Box 10)
        - Marsuppini Tomb (Box 10)
      - Washington (Box 10)
        - Bust of a Little Boy (Box 10)
        - National Gallery (Box 10)
          - Various Titles (Box 10)
          - Christ Child (Box 10)
          - Lady (Box 10)
          - S. Jerome [Slide box 60] (Box 10)
          - S. John (Box 10)
    - Donatello, ca.1386-146 (Box 10)
      X Donato di Niccolo di
      - Various titles (Box 10)
      - Berlin (Box 10)
      - Florence (Box 10)
        - Baptistry (Box 10)
          - Coscia Tomb (Box 10)
            Xx under Michelozzo di Bartolommeo
        - Bargello (Box 10)
          - David (bronze) (Box 10)
          - David (marble) (Box 10)
          - S. Geroge (Box 10)
          - Niccolo da Uzzano (Box 10)
        - Duomo (Box 10)
          - Various titles (Box 10)
          - S. John the Evangelist (Box 10)
          - Cantoria (Box 10)
          - Habakkuk [Slide box 61] (Box 11)
        - Jeremiah (Box 11)
          - Mary Magdalena (Box 11)
        - OrSanmichele (Box 11)
          - Various titles (Box 11)
        - Pal. Vecchio (Box 11)
          - Judith and Holofernes (Box 11)
        - S. Croce (Box 11)
          - Annunciation (Box 11)
          - Crucifix (Box 11)
          - S. Louis of Toulouse (Box 11)
        - S. Lorenzo (Box 11)
          - Old Sacristy (Box 11)
          - North Pulpit [Slide box 62] (Box 11)
          - South Pulpit (Box 11)
      - Padua (Box 11)
        - Piazza Del Santo (Box 11)
          - Gattamelata (Box 11)
        - S. Antonio (Box 11)
          - Angel Panels [Slide boxes 62-63] (Box 11)
          - Crucifix [Slide box 63] (Box 11)
          - Figures (Box 11)
          - Virgin and Child (Box 11)
          - Ass of Rimini (Box 11)
          - Heart of the Miser (Box 11)
          - Irascible Son (Box 11)
          - Speaking Babe (Box 11)
      - Rome (Box 11)
      - Siena (Box 11)
      - Washington (Box 11)
    - Embriachi, Baldassare degli, 1390-1409 (Box 11)
    - Fabro, Luciano, 1936- (Box 11)
    - Fancelli, Giacomo, 1619-1671 (Box 11)
    - Fantoni, Ventorino (Box 11)
    - Fanzago, Cosimo, 1591-1678 (Box 11)
    - Fedi, Pio, 1815-1892 (Box 11)
    - Farfa (V.O. Tommasini), 1881-1964 (Box 11)
    - Ferrata, Ercole, 1610-1686 (Box 11)
    - Ferrucci, Andrea di Piero, 1465-1526 [Slide box 64] (Box 11)
    - Filarete, Antonio, 1400-1469 (Box 11)
      - Rome (Box 11)
        - Various Titles (Box 11)
    - Foggini, Giovanni B., 1652-1725 (Box 11)
    - Fontana, Annibale, 1540-1587 (Box 11)